(Why are you crying?)
(After my grandparents passed away,)
(I said I wanted to clean up the house.)
(The guys gladly came to help her.)
(In the house where everything stands still,)
(kimchi made by her grandparents is still in the same place.)
(Where are you guys looking at?)
(Or give her a hug.)
(Are you guys from a waste hauling service?)
(Comforting someone isn't their forte.)
(I wonder if I have to throw out this sofa.)
- You probably should. - Yes.
(Oh, you think so?)
(Or if you want, )
(should I take a picture of it and put it online to sell it?)
(Why would I sell this?)
(I was crying and then laughed like crazy.)
(I laughed so hard because of him. He seemed more flustered, though.)
Why would I sell this?
(My bad)
(Exploding in disappointment)
(Sinking their heads)
(I thought you wanted to throw it out.)
(These close friends get ready to work in an unusual way.)
(They may not be good at comforting her,)
(but when it comes to physical labor, he's confident.)
(Turning into Servant84)
(Pulling it out easily)
(Moobicideman has eyes only for weeds.)
(Grunting)
(Super Moobicideman, the destroyer of farming tools)
(They continue to clean up the yard in the rain.)
(A mound of weeds was piled up in the yard.)
(As the three of them worked together...)
(We worked really hard.)
I can see the path now.
(The yard stood clear and open.)
(The last step of the cleanup is splashing water on their back.)
I can make a lot of bubbles like this.
My gosh, it hits the spot.
(She's smiling from ear to ear thanks to the guys.)
- That's so refreshing. - My grandparents probably...
- witnessed a lot of things. - All good.
- All good? - All good.
- Let's wash up. - You have a towel, right?
- I do. - Okay.
(They're done splashing their back after the battle with the weeds.)
Gosh, the irritation caused by grass is pretty painful.
That stings.
This is the first time my skin got irritated by grass.
Your facial skin is irritated too.
You apply it first.
- Me first? - Yes.
That stings.
- My skin was irritated too. - Seriously.
- I thought it'd be the death of me. - Yes.
The grass rashes are pretty bad.
Have you ever felt your skin being itchy and prickly at the same time?
That drives you crazy.
The rashes swelled far more than mosquito bites.
Mosquito bites are nothing compared to this.
- The itchiness goes away easily. - Those rashes are painful.
- Could you apply it on my back? - Sure.
I have to touch your back too.
He touched everything starting with Ju Seung.
- Yes. - He touched everyone.
You touched the body of every male member on the show.
(A gentle touch with Sung Hwan)
Your back is so smooth.
(Gosh, you punk...)
Your skin is smoother than Sung Hwan's.
(Your skin is smoother than Sung Hwan's.)
- I've felt everyone's skin. - That stings.
Gosh, it stings.
Goodness, it stings so much.
- This part is red. - It stings.
It's not just on our skin.
- It got on our clothes. - Right?
- It kept poking at us? - There must be...
- invisible thorns or something. - Yes.
- Gosh, this was tough. - Just my feet.
This was really tough on them.
- Of course, they're thin. - It pierced through our pants.
- I should take them off. - Change your pants.
- You'll do it here? - Well...
(He takes off the work pants right away.)
- Change your pants. - You startled me.
- I have shorts on. - My gosh, it's us.
There are no inhibitions between us.
- He's wearing shorts underneath. - Yes.
Even if he weren't, we wouldn't have made a big deal.
Let's take a short break and continue.
First of all, let's rest up.
(Looking around)
I think it's better...
to leave the mirror and other stuff on the wall.
Kian84 has good momentum when he works.
- He wanted to keep working. - He told us we shouldn't rest.
- You'd want to keep resting. - My gosh.
- We had to be diligent. - You had to keep going.
The sun would go down soon.
- I want to keep the sofa. - You do?
As for this sofa,
- Don't put it up online. - I'll use bleach to clean it.
You can't use bleach for this.
(Shocked)
- You can't use bleach for this. - No?
You want to sell this and use bleach on this now?
Do you want to destroy the sofa?
I don't know if this is real leather or not.
- We can't use bleach. - It looks like real leather.
- Right? - You don't know for sure, though.
First of all, I don't think I can take down the photos.
Could you guys take down the photos?
The photos? Okay then. Let me take care of the photos.
Yes. I'll pull down all the wallpapers.
Let's go.
I'll take everything down...
- including our picture. - Yes.
But why do you want to take down the photos?
There's a leak.
I need to take down these photos...
- before I repair the house. - I see.
But I couldn't bring myself...
- to take them down. - Right.
You can't.
(He starts with their picture that was hanging in the center.)
Seriously. I really wanted to clear the walls.
(He carefully places down memory-filled photos one at a time.)
Gosh, your grandpa...
was a great handyman.
He fixed this tightly, so it wouldn't fall.
Gosh, you bet.
It was impossible for it to fall off.
He coiled everything up tightly.
(He quietly enters a room...)
(after taking down the pictures in the living room.)
Gosh, look at the spiderweb.
Oh, no.
(The photos embracing their history hang on the wall.)
I didn't think you could do it yourself.
(Kian84 takes down the photos carefully in her place.)
Yes.
She told me about it before I came here.
She said she couldn't take down their photos.
These photos had been hanging there since she was a kid.
I told her I'd help her with the photos.
I was really grateful.
Is this photo taken on their wedding anniversary?
Which one? Oh, that one?
- I got my grandparents... - Yes.
To take a family picture.
It was hanging in their bedroom.
(Special pictures prepared by Na Rae)
(She joined them as their lovely granddaughter.)
This feels weird.
We took down all the photos from the walls.
- Here too? - Yes.
Okay. Then could you push this for me?
- The massage chair? - Yes.
So I can remove the wallpapers.
To remove mold,
I have to remove the wallpapers and then apply bleach on the walls.
That must be done before putting up new wallpapers.
I had to dry the walls first.
- You had to do that in advance. - Yes, right.
One, two.
- My goodness. - One, two.
- One, two. - They helped me so much.
Isn't that really heavy?
- Yes. - It's heavy.
(Putting on the mask...)
Gosh, why is it so short?
(before they start working on the walls)
(Lifting)
All good.
- Gosh, this is amazing. - My gosh, this is amazing.
- He was such a good handyman. - What adhesive did he use?
- It won't come off? - This is basically armored up.
My grandpa was the walking encyclopedia of Illo.
MacGyver of Illo.
Look how thoroughly he stuck them together.
He attached the extension cord on it like it had been welded.
So his wife could use it well.
Everything was fixed tightly and neatly,
- so they were all aligned. - Yes.
- Perfectly. - The home appliances and all.
They never came off.
- In hindsight, - Yes.
He must've done that for my grandma since she had trouble walking.
If she were to grab it and then fall,
it would lead to a huge accident.
- So he fixed them tightly. - He must've coiled everything...
and installed handles all over the house.
- My gosh. - Yes.
(When the guys are taking care of the furniture...)
Your wallpapering knowledge is coming in handy now.
Right.
(The guys follow Wallpapering Park's lead...)
(and work diligently.)
I used to sleep in here all the time.
I used to sleep with my grandparents here.
- This was their room? - Yes.
- This room? - Yes.
Hey, is this the wallpaper from your childhood?
- It's the same wallpaper. - It is?
Yes.
This wallpaper has seen you grow up.
Right. It's been there since I was a kid.
Gosh, this must feel strange for you.
Yes. So doing this makes me feel so liberated.
You took the wallpapering course because this had been...
- your plan all along, right? - That's right.
My grandparents never hired anyone to work on the house.
- Right. - I wanted to do the same.
(Her grandparents' house needed a lot of repairs.)
(To fix the house herself, )
(she learned how to hang wallpapers and apply plaster.)
It felt great to be able to use what I had learned.
It all paid off.
(I'll put up a beautiful wallpaper next time I come back.)
- When we were younger, - Yes.
If our romantic fling turned into a real relationship,
we would've been a married couple, pulling down the wallpapers, right?
- And we would work together? - That's the best life.
(They're working while exchanging silly jokes.)
(Grunting)
- My gosh. - What's going on?
Is there an old man around here? I hear someone groaning.
He's just getting old.
Hyun Moo never had to do hard labor.
(The grunting man who never had to do hard labor)
He was trying to show that he was working hard.
(Grunting)
(Super Moobicideman is working hard.)
(Clearing the weeds while sweating profusely)
- Let's do this. - You're sweating?
You touched the grass again after getting the rashes.
I was too scared to touch them again.
The waste truck was going to come back soon.
I had to load it up quickly.
All right. Go.
- Gosh. - We had to stay busy.
(They pick up speed before the waste truck arrives.)
Na Rae, give that to me. I'll take care of it.
No. I can take them out together.
(Being thorough even to the end)
(The waste truck arrives in no time.)
It's here.
(Clueless of the truck's arrival, they're focused on cleaning.)
This is good-quality leather.
Yes. This is real leather.
(Excuse me!)
Can we load up the container box?
Sure.
- I see. You cover it up first. - Yes.
(Covering it with a net before loading it)
- That way, things won't fall off. - Yes.
Hold on, sir!
- You can pile that on. - Okay.
- Right here. - Give me a bit more time.
- What do you need to do? Come here. - Wait.
Right here. I've got an opening here.
- You do? - Come here.
I wanted to get rid of the trash in a hurry.
- We needed to load everything up. - Yes.
Push everything in.
- What's that? - I got it.
- You're throwing out the ice box? - Yes.
Like students who want to write down answers...
- I'm sorry about this. - when time's up.
(Finishing up like students cramming at the last minute)
That's when you start spotting...
- a lot of trash. - Yes.
All the answers you put down now...
- turn out to be correct too. - Yes.
We're good now.
My gosh, we got a lot of things done.
Sir, how much weight can the container carry?
The container can carry about 4t.
About 4t?
- My gosh, 4t. - We collected 4t of trash.
- You'll probably need... - Let that go.
Another container of this.
- Right. - She'll need...
- two more of that. - Yes.
I'm a maximalist for a reason.
My grandma was a bigger maximalist...
- than me. - Seriously.
But you guys helped me with the first step.
The 1st step? Does it mean there's a 2nd step for us?
Listen.
- Call Ju Seung and Sung Hwan next. - Yes.
- You'll end late at night then. - Yes.
They're not good workers.
You guys are the best workers.
- Seriously. - Of course.
(Thanks to them, they collected a lot of trash.)
Gosh, we did so well.
I can't believe we filled that up.
- I can't believe this. - My gosh.
Can he actually load that onto the truck?
- The truck might topple over. - My gosh.
(The 4t container starts tilting.)
(Is it going to be okay?)
He struggled to load it onto the truck.
- My gosh. - That was scary.
(Spitting out)
(He quickly grabs the bucket that falls out.)
- Let's keep that here. - Let's throw it out next time.
It was meant to stay.
- Bye. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Bye.
Can't I just throw this in?
Gosh, how did we manage to do all this?
Right. How did you guys fill that up?
- This is just unbelievable. - My gosh.
The three of you did it.
(It's time to say goodbye at last.)
- Gosh, it looks clean now. - Yes.
Well done.
It felt like getting my wisdom tooth out.
I didn't need to get it out because it was rotten or anything.
I knew I had to get it done.
But I kept pushing it off. Then once I did it,
I was glad I did it.
It really gave me a liberating feeling.
(As deep as her love for them was,)
(the wisdom tooth was stuck just as painfully.)
(She didn't have the courage to pull it out.)
It really was the first step.
- You guys did a great job. - You did well.
- It looks the way it did before. - You did so well.
(Turning it back just as it used to be)
- Gosh, you guys did a great job. - Oh, my.
It looks clean now.
It's clean now.
I couldn't have done it without their help.
I couldn't have made it inside.
Right. This is liberating.
First of all, I pulled out something that wasn't a weed.
I made a lot of mistakes too.
But it was rewarding.
It turned back to the yard I once recognized.
It was a spacious yard.
It gave me a liberating feeling...
when I saw the yard was somewhat tidied up.
- It was quite rewarding. - It was very rewarding.
Even if it takes time,
I'll come down and fix up the house little by little.
I want my relatives and family to come to this house...
and remember our grandparents.
It'd be nice to invite my friends from time to time.
I just don't want this house...
to disappear.
- Okay. Let's grill meat. - Yes.
- Let's cook ramyeon. - Yes.
Who's going to cook ramyeon? Me?
Yes. I think it's okay to eat my grandma's kimchi. Right?
He's eyeing it.
Let's just eat half a head of cabbage.
(I doubt you can eat your grandma's kimchi.)
(Isn't it better if we eat it for you?)
In case she throws it out.
- That's it, right? - Yes.
- I wouldn't. - I hate wasting food. That's all.
Since I don't have anything to do while you guys cook,
I'll sort out the pictures.
- The ones he took down earlier? - Yes.
- Wipe them. - Yes.
- I'll help you too. - We should get...
the charcoal and meat then.
Me too?
Then help me with the pictures.
Which task is easier?
Come on.
All of my clothes are ruined.
- Who told you to wear them? - Right.
- Who wears clothes like them there? - Come on.
Who wears that kind of outfit to the countryside?
Gosh, this is crazy. People see me as a fashionista.
By the way, what's that thing on your head?
- Isn't that a mask? - The mask from earlier.
I didn't want my hairline to look thin.
- For real? - That's why?
(Your hair is thinning.)
(Thin)
- That's why I did that. - I had no idea.
- You thought it was for style? - Yes.
You must have hurt Moorincess' feelings.
(Feeling bitter)
I'll get the charcoal ready then.
- We don't have the brazier here. - Okay.
- Fill the cauldron with charcoal. - Yes.
- You can do that. - This should work.
- We can put the grill on top. - Yes.
All right.
(They bring out the frames, so they can wipe the frames.)
We need to dust the frames.
Na Rae, who are they?
They're my cousins.
- I'm the one on the bottom. - Okay.
- This is you? Right here? - Yes.
Yes.
This is you? How old were you then?
You look like you started school late.
You were a kid then?
- She looks determined. - Yes.
I ruled my neighborhood back then.
It's my graduation photo from kindergarten.
- From kindergarten? - Yes.
Not from the Lifelong Education Center?
- Lifelong Education? - Why do I look so old?
- Are you sure? - Yes.
Gosh, it's so dusty.
- It was so dusty. - All right.
- All right. - He wiped everything.
- Gosh, it was so dusty. - It easily collects dust.
Once you finish putting up the new wallpaper,
they will look great...
- on the wall. - Right.
I'll go and bring the meat and everything in the fridge.
- Okay. - Just start the fire.
(Hyun Moo goes in to grab the ingredients.)
- Kian84. - Yes?
You worked a lot today.
- Eat this? - What's that?
I'm so exhausted.
We worked a lot today.
Since we're tired, let's take one each.
At this rate, we might pass out.
(Let's recover from fatigue before we pass out.)
Taking this supplement will make a huge difference.
- We should take one. - Yes.
- You should. - We should.
(Swallowing)
This is nice.
We must start taking supplements.
We're not those young people from eight years ago.
(Let's get started now that my energy is up.)
- I'll set it up here. - Sure.
My gosh.
(Adding the charcoal to the cauldron)
- Do you want the meat now? - What?
- Do you want the meat? - Yes.
I'll bring it over once you start the fire.
- Hyun Moo. - Yes.
I brought a photo album.
Put the photos in it then.
- Sure. - It's in my bag.
You brought an empty photo album?
He bought one.
Our photo album was too old.
She told me that she had a lot of pictures.
I bought one, so we could organize them.
(He comes out with the album and meat.)
Here.
(Passing the meat to Na Rae)
(Blazing up)
It looks like their roles have switched.
(Starting the fire without hesitation)
- How sharp. - It felt natural for us, though.
(Sitting down delicately)
Everyone can just do what they're good at.
- Gosh, look at the dust. - Goodness, it's nice and breezy.
- The breeze feels refreshing. - I can breathe again.
Seriously. Thank you for your hard work.
I'll arrange them myself.
- Okay. - I mean, the photos.
(Aligning them neatly)
My gosh.
When was that taken?
(This looks different from now.)
Hey, the door used to be here.
- Yes. - Is that the same house?
Yes. It's exactly the same house.
Only the door was moved.
Is it okay that I'm arranging...
- your grandparents' photos? - Yes.
I'm trying to tell a story with the photos.
I think it will be too much on me.
- Is that so? - Yes.
They look young in the picture.
They were young in this picture.
You guys are a real family.
- They were young. - Right.
You're paying attention while arranging them.
(Na Rae gets ready to grill meat.)
Na Rae, you look like the owner of a famous restaurant.
- Yes. - Right.
You arranged the pork belly like how it looked in the photos.
Gosh, you bet. I have my own story to tell with the pork belly.
(Using the torch on the neatly arranged pork belly)
I should let the oil drip.
I needed the oil to drip...
- to start the fire. - That's it.
- It was so good. - Yes.
My gosh. Darn it.
(Falling out)
- Oh, no. - My gosh.
Darn it.
(Glancing over)
(She's grilling the meat for the hard-working guys.)
- My gosh. Darn it. - Oh, no.
- You can pick it up quickly. - Yes.
- It's okay. Put it back. - Yes. Let's do that.
- No. - No, don't throw it out.
- You might die from it. - I'll eat that.
- My gosh. - Your appendix will burst.
- Why throw it out? Put it back. - I won't eat it!
- Put it back on the grill! - No! I won't eat that.
- I'll never eat it. - I'll eat that.
- No, don't do it. - Let me just...
(Anxious)
(Calm down, guys.)
- Put it back on the grill! - No! I won't eat that.
- I'll never eat it. - I'll eat that.
- No, don't do it. - Let me just...
- I'll eat that. - I won't eat it.
- I'll eat that. - Your appendix will burst.
- It will be my appendix bursting. - Shut it.
- Let me wash it with water. - I won't eat it.
- My gosh. - I'll eat that.
(Bickering over meat)
- Just rinse it with water. - Seriously.
- I don't eat dirty food. - I won't eat it.
- I said I'd eat it. - It's got soil on it.
And it's muddy here. No, don't do it.
- It's okay. - No, don't do it.
This is why your immune system is weak.
What are you talking about?
Your immune system gets weak from eating food like that.
- Just rinse it with water. - Rinse it with water.
- No. - He was dead set against it.
- Never. - Just rinse it with water.
I hate dirty things.
And the soil is full of germs.
- That's my point. - The fire would kill them all.
No. It doesn't work like that.
You could die from it.
- Our lives are too sheltered. - Right.
- You could die from it. - Just pretend that it's clean...
and just eat it.
- Yes. - Yes. Do that.
- Yes. - You did that?
No, I just washed it.
It was on the ground for a second.
Then the meat will just burn without getting cooked.
No, I'm watching it constantly.
(Acting as if nothing happened)
(Glancing back)
- Look. It looks so milky-white. - Come on.
- Did I eat that? - It looks so clean.
(The meat is getting grilled nicely.)
I'm doing an amazing job with this.
- Na Rae, put it back. It's a waste. - Yes, I'll do that.
Put what back? Don't.
- I'll eat the one that fell. - No. Don't eat it.
- You shouldn't eat dirty food. - You shouldn't.
Why eat something that fell into the muddy water?
We all start in the soil and return to it anyway.
- What's so bad about... - You'll have a quick return then.
But pigs grow up around the soil.
- Yes. - Of course.
Why don't you just grill meat on the dirt?
Just place it on the dirt and torch it.
- Wipe off the dirt afterward. - Seriously.
That way, I won't drop it.
(The rinsed meat is getting cooked nicely.)
- Gosh, she grilled it well. - Kian84.
(Smacking his lips)
Kian84.
- I'm nearly done grilling meat. - Okay.
- Once I wrap this up, - Okay.
I'll bring kimchi.
Would it really be okay to eat your grandma's kimchi?
It's okay.
I felt like Grandma would be happy to see us eat it.
That's right.
(Taking out her grandma's kimchi...)
(makes her feel conflicted)
I know that Grandma's kimchi is here.
(Let's see.)
It's here. It's aged kimchi.
It was made in 2022.
(Aged kimchi her grandma made in 2022)
- Year of 2022? - Year of 2022.
- It's three years old. - Yes.
It had an address on the top.
She was going to send it to my place.
Was the address yours?
She couldn't send it, so it was right there.
(She opens the aged kimchi.)
This won't do.
Since it was made in 2022...
- You can eat it. - You can eat it.
That's right.
Since it's only yeast,
I can rinse it and eat it.
You can rinse it and make kimchi jjigae with it.
I didn't know that you could save it.
- You can save it. - I see.
Isn't the bottom part like that?
- No, not at all. - The bottom part looks fine.
- Hyun Moo. - Yes?
(Hyun Moo)
- I don't think... - Yes?
- we can eat this kimchi. - Why not?
- Well... - Did it go bad?
We could rinse it and eat it, but it'd be a bit...
You should be the judge. We don't need to eat it.
Let's make ramyeon. We don't need to eat it.
I wanted to treat them to a nice meal.
But the white stuff isn't mold.
You can remove it, rinse the kimchi, and eat it.
But I couldn't include that kimchi in the meal...
for Hyun Moo and Kian84.
I felt like my grandma would be upset.
Both my grandma and grandpa told me...
that I needed to treat my guests well.
They would've scolded me if I had served that kimchi.
I'll give you a nice meal.
- Okay. I'll look forward to it. - It'll be a proper feast.
- Here. - My goodness.
These things were in the house.
- Okay. - What?
- Disposable chopsticks. - Disposable chopsticks? Nice.
(Na Rae brings disposable items and a pot.)
Gosh, it's an enamel pot.
- You haven't seen one, right? - Yes.
It's really old.
- Grandma used it well. - It looks nice.
- They don't throw away such items. - It looks cute.
- I think Grandma will scold me... - Why?
For mistreating my guests.
Don't be ridiculous.
Had she been alive, she would've scolded me so badly.
This is enough. We have meat and ramyeon.
This is enough. We just need ramyeon.
- Still, I feel bad. - It's okay.
I'll cook ramyeon.
I have confidence in my ramyeon-cooking skills.
- Adjust the volume of water. - I'll do that.
The thing is,
I had something delivered by someone I know.
Like what?
- Do you have acquaintances here? - Of course.
It's makgeolli!
(Heave-ho)
- Nice. - Is it makgeolli?
It's makgeolli.
Take some bottles later.
You can't order fewer than 20 bottles at a time...
- if you want them delivered. - Really? I'll take some bottles.
- Why did no one come to help? - My goodness.
She would've felt uncomfortable.
(What?)
Most people pretend to get up...
- even if they don't want to help. - I know.
That would've been more unbecoming.
Most people would've yelled from a distance, "Isn't it heavy?"
They would've gone, "Oh, my!" They didn't do anything.
INTPs are clear-cut.
They don't pretend if they don't want to do something.
They don't even go, "Oh, my!"
I'm not surprised.
- What kind of makgeolli is it? - Is it makgeolli?
- Yes. - Where is it from?
It's unpasteurized makgeolli.
(It's even unpasteurized makgeolli.)
- It's... - Give me one.
The lager in the makgeolli scene.
- The lager in the makgeolli scene? - The taste is so clean.
That's why unpasteurized makgeolli has a shorter shelf life.
Good makgeolli has a short shelf life.
Yes.
Hey, Na Rae. Wait, what was his name?
For goodness' sake.
- Take it. - You got confused.
- All done. The meat is all done. - It's all done.
The meat looks tasty.
- It's all done. - You get that at a barbecue place.
- It nearly looks like bacon. - Yes.
Hey, this meal is too simple. Seriously.
- It isn't simple at all. - I'm so embarrassed.
- Seriously. - Take this.
This is great.
- Take this. - Gosh, thank you.
- Thank you for your hard work. - All right.
That's the spirit, Hyun Moo.
- Cheers. - Thank you for your hard work.
For Grandpa and Grandma.
Grandma.
You should've said something before downing it.
- Grandma. For goodness' sake. - Oh, my.
(I was too thirsty.)
It's okay.
It's light.
That was why I called it lager. The taste is clean.
The taste is clean.
- It isn't rich. - No.
(He takes a bite of the heavily grilled pork belly.)
(Impressed)
Look at the inside.
It's insane.
It's so juicy.
- Nice. - Why is unseasoned meat so tasty?
Did you season it with salt?
- No. - No.
Kian84, it's so tasty.
- He grilled it well. - It's so tasty.
It was tasty.
- It was really tasty. - Yes.
That sentimentality is nice.
Hyun Moo, hurry up and cook ramyeon.
Wait.
- We cleaned everything, right? - Yes.
Camellia flowers will grow over there in winter.
It'll be nice to look at the camellia flowers in winter.
Are we coming back in winter?
I'm a bit scared to come back here.
Don't be scared. Come here to rest then.
- To rest? - Don't do anything.
- I work a lot whenever I see you. - No way.
Even if you come here to rest, there'll be some work to do.
- I know. - No way.
We need to work on the outer walls.
- He needs to draw murals. - Yes.
Kian84 is good at it.
Thank you.
(You know how I feel, right?)
For you guys...
- I hope this never happens. - Okay.
But I'm willing to give you a kidney.
- Really? - Why would you give me a kidney?
I'll keep that in mind.
To be honest, I could just hire a cleaning company.
Right.
But they wouldn't have wiped the photos.
While professional cleaners are good,
- it's meaningful for us to do it. - It's meaningful.
That's right. We have memories of this place.
Thank you for taking down the photos.
I wanted to take them down, but couldn't bear to do it.
- It would've been too much for you. - Yes.
You wouldn't have been able to do it.
Of course not.
I was so thankful.
(She's thankful for the people who understand her.)
- I'm sorry to ruin the moment, - Okay.
- but I'm so good at making ramyeon. - This is great.
- It's insane. - Sprinkle some pepper.
- Shall I add some pepper? - It'll be nice.
- What has gotten into you? - Ramyeon tastes good with pepper.
- Really? - Yes.
(Sprinkling)
Aren't you sprinkling too much?
- Hyun Moo! - That's too much.
It's okay because there's a lot of water.
It's like this only on the surface.
- Seriously. - It became jjajang ramyeon.
Don't be ridiculous.
- Will you work as well? - Yes. Isn't it too short?
Seriously.
It's spicy for him too.
See? You sprinkled too much.
(The added amount makes even Pepper Brother sneeze.)
- I made it a bit salty. - A bit salty.
- We need salt after sweating. - That's right.
- It looks tasty. - It's good to make it a bit salty.
The texture is firm and the taste is peppery.
(Slurping)
(Impressed)
Seriously.
It's insanely tasty!
You should admit it.
I eyeballed the amount of water.
I'm better than the ramyeon machines at the Han River.
(His eyeball measurement beats the ramyeon machines.)
Seriously, Hyun Moo made it well.
How is it so tasty?
You can't beat me when it comes to ramyeon.
- It's insanely tasty. - It's tasty.
Food you eat after labor is really tasty.
(They enjoy ramyeon after taxing labor.)
It's good.
The air was cool after the rain.
(They eat as they cool their sweat in the cool evening wind.)
It's really tasty.
Have a drink.
- Have a drink. - Okay.
- You worked hard. - You worked hard.
I'll treat you to a nice meal.
(Hold on.)
I think my grandma will scold me for not giving you...
better drinking snacks.
(What is it?)
I'm taking it out even though I cherish it a lot.
- What? What is it? - What is it?
It's the salt cured fish roe I made.
(The salt cured fish roe Na Rae made)
The salt cured fish roe.
- Did you make it? - Yes.
You need to wipe it twice a day.
(She learned the method...)
(from the salt cured fish roe master at Mount Jiri.)
About four weeks.
For three weeks,
I wiped it twice a day with Munbaeju.
Now, I keep it...
in a vacuum-sealed bag.
I flipped it over twice a day.
That's a lot of work.
- We don't have a knife. - There we go.
Take a small piece and taste it.
You're absolutely incredible.
- How did you make that? - He sprinkled so much pepper.
- He added more. - I should've known.
I did it when they weren't looking.
(Unaware, they focus on slicing the salt cured fish roe.)
It's working.
A bit at a time.
- Try a small bit. - I'm really curious about it.
- It's so precious. - It's so precious.
I'll eat it as it is.
Okay. Eat a small bit at a time. It's salty.
- It's really tasty. - It's so tasty.
- I love the chewy texture. - Yes.
(Smacking his lips)
(Impressed)
I'm getting drunk.
I'm getting drunk on the salt cured fish roe.
Ramyeon with salt cured fish roe.
(Let's try ramyeon with salt cured fish roe.)
They don't even sell it in Naples.
They have salt cured fish roe pasta, but not that.
No.
It's chewy.
It's a bit funky.
The oily taste hits you belatedly.
It's such a luxury.
When I made salt cured fish roe,
I thought that I'd eat it on a special day.
Today is a special day.
(With people who are dear to her,)
(she eats salt cured fish roe without reservation.)
(Impressed)
It's such a luxury.
I'm getting drunk.
(As they enjoy delicious food, the night deepens.)
The thing is...
(The thing is...)
There's a Jindo dog my grandpa had.
- It's named Bokdol. - Okay.
- The dog at the animal hospital? - Yes.
(Grandpa's dog was sent to the animal hospital...)
(for a checkup.)
- It's at the animal hospital. - Is it at the animal hospital?
- It's named Bokdol. - Okay.
My grandpa was the one who came up with the name, Bokdol.
In a sense, that dog is your grandpa's child.
The breed is called hogu.
- Hogu? - Hogu?
Baekgu, hwanggu, and heukgu are the types of Jindo dogs.
- Like the word for "A pushover?" - Yes.
No. The meaning is different.
Hyun Moo is a pushover.
I'm a pushover. Both of us are pushovers.
It's a Jindo dog with tiger patterns.
- "Ho" means "Tiger." - I know this type of Jindo dogs.
Grandpa had it for two and a half years.
For dogs, two and a half years is a long period of time.
For about six months after Grandpa passed away,
it didn't eat dog food when Uncle tried to feed it.
- Jindo dogs are loyal. - Yes.
The thing is, I... I bet I told you this once.
To be honest, ever since Grandpa passed away...
It has been over two years, right?
I thought about the dog constantly.
I gave it some thought earlier.
While I shouldn't tell people what they should or shouldn't do...
- It's okay. But I... - Why don't you take the dog?
Really?
Will I be a good owner?
As for that...
I think that dog will bring you good fortune.
- Its name is Bokdol. - I believe in such things.
Also, you could say...
that your grandpa left you...
- He left me the dog. - Yes. He left you the dog.
- Take the dog in. I'll help you. - That's right.
(Really?)
I'll send you some dog food. Feed the dog.
Take it home for now.
If things get too tough, I'll recommend a training center.
I'll take the dog tomorrow.
- Tomorrow? - That's right.
The dog is currently in Itaewon.
- At your place? - Bokdol is at my place. Yes.
I'm learning new things with Hyun Moo's help.
We've been messaging each other a lot because of that.
- That's right. - You should let the dog adjust.
Bokdol is living well in Seoul.
- Seriously, give it a go. - What?
For goodness' sake.
Why is it raining so suddenly?
It's nice and cool.
It began raining after we finished eating ramyeon.
I can't believe it.
- Gosh, this is... - For goodness' sake.
It's nice. Let's just eat.
- I'll lose hair again. - Really?
Why is it raining so suddenly?
- Heavy rain began so suddenly. - I think it'll stop raining soon.
I think your grandparents watched over us today.
Had it been hot like it said on the weather forecast,
I would've passed out.
I could keep going thanks to the cool wind.
That's right. We would've passed out.
- Yes. Like that, it rained. - It wasn't hot.
- It was sunny when we grilled meat. - That's right.
Since it's raining,
I don't know if I can give it to you.
What?
You know,
the weather worsened when I was about to give a present.
(A present?)
What is it?
You know,
the weather worsened when I was about to give a present.
(The weather worsened when I was about to give a present.)
- It's raining so much. - My present...
shouldn't get rained on.
Shouldn't it get rained on?
Then show it to us quickly.
Hold on. Let me bring an umbrella.
It has been so long since I drank in the rain.
(Screaming)
- Are you okay? - My hip joints are ruined.
- Oh, no. - My hip joints were destroyed.
The rain feels so cool.
It's so cool.
Even if I get rained on,
- my present shouldn't. - What is it?
What?
It stopped raining just in time for us to open the present.
- Right? - Isn't it really fascinating?
Oh, my.
Hurry up and open it.
- Well... - I'm curious too.
What is it?
- This present contains my love. - Okay.
Just think that it contains my love.
You didn't need to bring anything. You worked so hard today.
I didn't expect to receive anything.
- It's nothing big. - What is it?
- Look that way. - What?
Turn around.
- Turn around? - That's right.
Just what did you prepare?
Seriously.
At the same time?
- They need to be together. - I see.
What is it?
It's...
Late at night,
I put in a lot of work.
- What is it? - Take a look. One, two, three.
(She becomes emotional as soon as she sees the present.)
- Oh, my. - Are those paintings?
(Hyun Moo painted Na Rae's grandpa and grandma.)
Your painting skills have improved a lot.
Hyun Moo, you did a good thing.
(Korean passport)
They're your best paintings yet.
Seriously.
(They're your best paintings yet.)
I thought about the past.
(Clearing his throat)
(Seeing Hyun Moo choke up makes her cry even more.)
You should keep them at a nice place.
What's that?
- What's that? - I added these details...
because Grandpa said that he wanted to travel the world.
I made him a passport...
and drew an airplane.
- So that he could travel? - Yes.
It was his dream to travel around the world.
(Grandpa, why do you want a globe?)
(Since I'm too old to travel, I want to do it through the globe.)
(For Grandpa who dreamed of traveling around the world)
It's meaningful.
And when I think about your grandma...
- You recognize it, right? - Yes.
Farming chili peppers come to mind first.
(With Na Rae's grandma who had the brightest smile,)
(he made unforgettable memories in summer.)
- I have good memories. - He's a very good painter.
(She misses her grandma and grandpa.)
I painted them. I thought...
it'd be nice to hang them up somewhere in the house.
I see.
- Gosh, Hyun Moo. - My grandparents will love them.
- Really? - Yes.
I thought about ways to revive the energy of the house.
While I lack the skills,
I'm the painter who touches people's hearts.
- He's saying that about himself. - So...
- No one did, so I had to. - Today, it's true.
- It's true. - Yes.
- Today, it's true. - Yes.
I took out all the paints I had at home.
If I had more time, I would've made...
- bigger paintings with more care. - It's okay.
But I focused on putting my heart into it.
Even before I started painting,
I thought about where to put the heart.
I added the heart at the very end.
(I added the heart at the very end after much consideration.)
In the afterlife, I hope they'll hold hands...
and make many happy memories together.
I painted with that thought.
The thing is, I'm a very rational person.
I'm not the type to get emotional...
and shed tears.
But I got emotional.
It must be because I'm aging.
If you give a painting as a present, you usually paint the recipient.
You don't paint what the recipient misses.
That was...
- what I really liked. - I never imagined it.
(Well...)
Among Hyun Moo's paintings, they were the best.
You really are Moosquiat.
- Now, - Now, he's good.
He has established his style.
Seriously, I've said it before.
They didn't seem like someone else's grandparents.
I thought about the past and watched the old videos.
She really looks like my grandma.
I would've done better...
- if I had more time. - It's okay.
I love your present.
I felt like a member of that family.
She feels like an actual younger sister now.
- She really feels that way. - She may be more muscular than me,
but my heart broke for her throughout the day.
We spent many years together and went through many hardships.
We've left many memories together.
We're a family.
Hyun Moo is my eldest older brother.
He embraces us, understands us,
and watches over us. He gives us good advice too.
Kian84 is my second eldest older brother.
There are people who take care of you while grumbling, right?
They feel just like my older brothers.
We are like brothers in arms,
but we never get discharged from the army.
He said something completely different.
I lost count with our ranks now.
We're like brothers in arms who never get discharged.
We're soldiers for life.
You're so good. It's making me reflect upon myself.
- What are you saying? - What? It's raining again!
(What? It's raining again!)
- Gosh! - Hurry!
- Let's put them in here. - Here.
- Gosh. - It's okay.
(Rushing in case his work gets wet)
They can't be rained on.
Gosh, it's raining all of a sudden.
I got so surprised.
It rained all of a sudden...
- as soon as we looked at them. - Right.
They must be watching us.
- My gosh. - How was it timed like that?
- Gosh! - Na Rae!
I have a gift for you as well.
You have a gift for her as well?
My gift for you is labor.
That works as a gift.
- Right. - Kian84.
I came here to work like a dog.
Right. You're the best!
I will make sure to repay the two of you.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
It suddenly rained so much.
Hello!
- Gosh, everyone went wild... - Gosh.
After last week's Rainbow Live trailer.
- Everyone went wild. - Right.
In my sentimental playlist that I listen to these days,
I have a lot of this group's songs.
Really?
That is why I really wanted to meet this person.
I think he's the most good-looking drummer that I know.
- Gosh. - Right.
For the first time as a Korean band,
all seats of Gocheok Sky Dome were sold out.
The driving force of Korea's band boom.
It's DAY6's drummer, Dowoon!
(DAY6's drummer, Dowoon)
(A band boom will come. No. It has already come with DAY6.)
("Goyang Stadium Sold Out, KSPO DOME's Largest Audience")
("First K-Band to Enter Gocheok Sky Dome")
(To the refreshing sound, )
(the drummer breathes in life.)
(DAY6, Dowoon)
- You were beautiful - You were beautiful
(Bowing)
- Hello. - Hello.
He's standing next to me. Gosh, he's handsome.
- He's handsome. - He's handsome.
I'm Yoon Dowoon, the one who plays the drums for DAY6.
- It's a pleasure to meet you. - Yes!
Can we ask how you feel?
I've always watched this show on TV.
I'm feeling nervous to be here myself.
- He has a strong accent. - Busan?
- Are you from Gyeongsang Province? - Are you from Busan?
I'm from the Changwon and Busan area.
He has a pretty face,
but he smells like a macho.
I can tell right away as I'm a macho myself.
(It's great to see you, my fellow macho.)
Hasn't it been a while since you've moved to Seoul?
It has been almost ten years.
But your accent still feels quite strong.
I didn't find the need to change my accent.
He sounds so charming. It's great to hear.
Gosh, thank you.
- Don't get rid of your accent. - Got it.
(A Man's Day)
"A Man's Day."
(Rustling)
(Fascinated)
Gosh, you keep it so dark as you're a man.
(Vibrating)
Hello.
It is currently 2:40am.
- It's 2:40am? - It is 19°C.
- Why wake up at this hour? - The lowest temperature is 16°C.
- Sean doesn't get up at this hour. - The highest temperature is 27°C.
He would be fast asleep at this hour.
Bixby.
Turn off the air conditioner in the bedroom.
Okay.
(He wakes up with Bixby.)
(Getting up)
(He walks out.)
Hello.
I'm Yoon Dowoon, and I play the drums for DAY6.
It has been 5 to 6 years since I've lived alone.
It has been 4 to 5 months...
since I've lived in this house.
I'm an outsider when it comes to interior design.
A person that I know does interior design.
That was how I got the interior design done...
for this place.
I go on a lot of tours abroad.
- "Tours abroad." - I hated the hotel vibes.
I just wanted this place to feel like home.
- "Like home." - A place I can rest in.
It's nice.
- It's neat. - I love that it's neat.
Nice and neat like home.
A minimalistic design mixed with some wood.
He must like keeping things minimal.
(The minimal home of a man)
(There's just a bed in the bedroom.)
It does feel quite empty.
There isn't anything else.
(The computer room is neat too.)
It's neat in here too.
(The kitchen is minimal too.)
Gosh, there isn't any furniture.
- It's like a rental home. - It's so neat.
Really?
(The dressing room is filled only with clothes.)
You must not be interested in home accessories.
I did place a few.
But they're all small.
- They're small? - Yes.
These are aquatic plants.
- In my previous house, - So you like aquatic plants.
I didn't get any sunlight.
I couldn't grow plants as they all died.
I'm growing a lot of them now with the sun.
So there were accessories.
- Right. - They were just small.
Right. They're small points in the house.
"Small points."
How cute.
(He goes to the kitchen right after getting up.)
What's going on?
(Empty)
That isn't your house, right?
- It is my house. - It's a rental home, right?
- Be clear with us. - No. It's my house.
- Are you sure? - What is that?
Our band suddenly became popular.
We had to work every single day.
"Suddenly became popular?"
I only ordered food.
That feels like a refrigerator of a star.
(Laughing)
How long has it taken to reach this far?
- It took us 10 years. - It took you guys 10 years?
The long-term investment was a success.
JYP's long-term investment.
- Bands with handsome members. - Bands with handsome members.
There were no bands like that for a while.
- CNBLUE was the last one. - There were none after CNBLUE.
- Right. - F.T. Island as well.
- DAY6 was like a band from a drama. - Right.
- Gosh. - That was how they felt.
Gosh.
- That's a great compliment. - After they appeared,
more bands came to life.
It's an honor for us.
(Drinking cold water on an empty stomach)
It's so neat.
It's great as it's so neat.
(Brushing)
(He brushes his tongue like a man.)
(Retching)
It even shows me retching.
I thought you were going to reach your stomach.
It's fascinating to watch me live my life.
(He brushes his teeth and washes his face at once as a man.)
(He washed his face just with water.)
(He heads somewhere without applying any lotion.)
(Opening)
What is all that?
They're fishing rods!
(There was a hidden room?)
I turned that place into...
a storage room slash fishing room.
So he enjoys fishing.
I see. This is the man's room.
Gosh, he must love fishing.
I absolutely love fishing.
- Gosh. That's his gear? - He seems to be an expert.
It seems like it's for sea fishing.
Right.
- Right. I enjoy jigging. - Sea fishing.
I've tried sea fishing quite a lot of times.
I go from time to time with my friends in Incheon.
- Right. - Right.
But we usually rent the fishing gear.
Right. He seems to be an expert.
He must know someone that is an expert.
The reason I woke up early...
was to go fishing.
I have pride in fishing.
I'm quite good at fishing.
- He's a man. - Gosh.
(The fishing channel that is a must for fisherman)
(Fishing instinct)
You were even on the fishing channel?
I appeared a lot.
FTV is a channel with experts.
- Right. - FTV is a channel...
that is kept on all the time for lovers of fishing.
Definitely.
It's a pleasure to be on that channel as a lover of fishing.
The biggest one that I caught was the 97.5cm yellowtail amberjack.
(Biggest catch: 97.5cm yellowtail amberjack)
- That's as big as Na Rae. - Right.
- There isn't much of a difference. - Right.
There's a fishing competition?
- Yes. - He competes as well?
(The man who loves the sea, Do Taigong)
To go fishing,
I've been to Geoje, Tongyeong,
Wando, and the Yellow Sea. I've been all around the country.
There's something called big-game fishing.
There's a rod used for amberjacks.
- You catch amberjacks too? - There's one for sea bass.
There's one for catching octopus.
There's one for webfoot octopus.
There's one for flatfish.
There's one for several kinds as well.
- I think that's about it. - He must love fishing.
(Opening)
(Shall I start getting out my fishing gear?)
(The room is filled with fishing gear.)
He's doing that at 2:30am.
What are you doing right now?
I'm getting out the fishing gear...
for the type of fish that I will be catching.
The things that I prepare are different...
based on what I catch.
The baits that the fish bite are different...
based on what kind of fish they are.
- Right. - Right.
(I'm done.)
(The life vest that is essential for boat fishing is packed.)
(He carefully prepares the rods as well.)
I have no idea what they all are.
We wouldn't know if he's that much of an expert.
I have no idea.
(He packed a lot of his gear.)
(It's still dark outside.)
(The man of the sea heads out from his house.)
So you wake up earlier than a runner if you go fishing.
What time did you sleep before waking up?
I slept at around 8 or 9pm.
That's enough sleep then.
That's a decent amount of sleep.
(Humming)
It's Sung Si Kyung's song.
(Sung Si Kyung's song)
You must go to a motel with that song.
(Dowoon is driving early in the morning.)
(Humming)
It's Sung Si Kyung's song.
You must go to a motel with that song.
(You must go to a motel with that song.)
Don't get the wrong idea.
He enjoys MA.
- He enjoys going to motels alone. - I see!
I got so surprised!
(He remembered the time he went to a motel alone...)
(after hearing Sung Si Kyung's song.)
- Gosh. - What were you thinking?
- No. - What were you thinking?
- I'm sorry. - He didn't know.
- Come on, Dowoon! - He didn't know.
I didn't expect you to be like that!
So...
- Gosh, he's turning red! - Why is your face turning red?
His face is so red!
- He's been having naughty thoughts. - Dowoon!
- His ears are completely red! - Your ears are bleeding right now.
(Blushing)
He's out of breath on his own.
"Is this okay?"
- Gosh. - "Is this okay?"
"Is this right?"
"Is this public television?"
(Is this public television?)
Gosh.
- How cute. That was hilarious. - How innocent of you.
(The innocent man)
(He plays the beat with his hands.)
You're playing to the song.
Right. It has a good bounce.
It was perfect to play on.
Bixby.
- What? - What?
(What?)
Someone's Bixby turned on.
It turned on after hearing that?
- Really? - Really?
(It turned on after hearing that?)
It was mine.
But it was Sung Hwan's Bixby.
It was Sung Hwan's?
- I'm sorry. - That's fascinating.
Hold on.
Why did yours turn on with Dowoon's voice?
Right. Our voices...
- must be similar. - They sound quite similar.
Does it recognize voice tones?
Will it not rain today?
(He heads to his destination while checking the weather.)
It will not rain today.
He's heading to Incheon?
Daebu Island.
Sihwa Seawall.
(Buzzing)
That's the sound of a hair clipper.
- Gosh. - What a man!
- That's impressive. - Inside the car?
He's shaving while driving.
- He's a true man. - Right.
(Fishing)
(Signs can be seen one by one.)
(He safely reaches his destination.)
(Let's get going.)
It's so dark.
What time was that?
It must've been around 4:30am to 5am.
- Gosh, that's so early. - That was why he got up at 2:30am.
That's amazing.
Usually, how often did you go fishing?
- Usually... - When you had more time.
When I had more time, I went for 3 to 4 days a week.
I rented a guest house.
- For 3 to 4 days a week? - That was what I did.
- You must love fishing. - I think I went for...
- at least 2 to 3 days a week. - He's serious about fishing.
- That's amazing. - He's a true lover of fishing.
It just feels so therapeutic to me.
You must have plans set as you have more time now.
I'll be going to Wando the day after tomorrow.
- Wando? - With whom?
The guy I was holding the fish with like this.
Captain Hwang.
I got close to the people who live there.
Captain Hwang is a big shot in Wando.
"Big shot."
I used to go fishing often with my friends.
It had been several months since I couldn't go fishing.
As today was my day off,
I planned to have a time of rest for myself.
(He diligently gears himself up.)
(He walks naturally even in the dark.)
The place that I went to...
was Jindu Wharf at the Yellow Sea.
There are so many boats.
(It's filled with fishermen early in the morning.)
There are so many people.
The species that I will catch today is the webfoot octopus.
- Webfoot octopus? - Yes.
- They are in season. - In September.
They are allowed to be caught in September.
- Gosh. - That's when they are in season.
People must've waited for this moment.
They must be filled with eggs.
- My mouth is watering already. - They taste great.
(Drooling)
I'm actually drooling.
(The webfoot octopus battle happens at around this time...)
(at the Yellow Sea.)
- I heard you could catch over 20. - It's really popular these days.
(Dowoon enters that battle.)
That must be exciting!
Gosh, hello. It's been a while.
It's a person he knows. It's the man with the boat.
I was late, wasn't I?
- It's been quite a while. - Thank you.
He's cold outside and warm inside.
(Grumbling)
"Come here!" This is how he feels.
I follow him a lot like my father of fishing.
Captains tend to sound like that.
Right.
I got on the captain's boat.
(Sailing with his father of fishing after a while)
Thank you.
I can really see that he loves fishing.
It's been so long since I've seen you.
It's the captain's wife.
(He writes his name on the passenger list.)
Here you are. Thank you.
- Do you need a vest? - I'm wearing one right now.
Vests are the pride of fishermen.
- You must have your own vest? - It's a must.
You must have your own vest.
Why? What goes inside the vest?
It's not about what goes inside.
It's saying, "I won't wear the standard vest..."
"that is on the boat."
"I won't wear the orange vest!"
It's like when snowboarders have their own suits.
Right. That's what it's like.
(As a seasoned fisherman, )
(he calmly prepares his gear while whistling.)
When you get on the boat, you have to get yourself prepared.
That's basic etiquette for fishing.
It feels like watching a fishing channel.
I think of the knotting method that is highly utilized.
It goes in the ring and gets twirled.
The two links...
are twirled around up to four times and pulled.
The knot is made when the original line is then pulled.
It's the uni knot.
It can be used a lot when camping as well.
I'm done!
(Shall I get my face ready as well?)
(Squeezing out the sunscreen)
(Applying in a tough manner)
- Gosh. - Gosh.
We're on the same line.
(The skincare routine of men)
- We will set sail. - Okay.
Get ready.
(He applies a generous amount of sunscreen before they set sail.)
- A lot must be applied. - Right.
- Your skin will eat it up anyway. - Right.
(Setting sail at 5:53am)
Even before the sun is out.
- Gosh. - The sunrise will look nice.
It feels like a drama scene.
Doesn't it look stunning?
I feel very excited.
I wonder if I can meet my expectations.
Gosh.
(Reel in with trust. There will be a bite.)
"Reel in with trust. There will be a bite."
He's the man of the sea.
(The man of sea sails with great passion.)
When I see the wonders of nature,
I realize how small I am in this world.
- "How small I am in this world." - "Small."
I can feel it from what you're saying.
Right.
Many things are insignificant compared to this world.
- Exactly. For sure. - Right.
(He goes through his pockets while keeping that in mind.)
(Let's have a chocolate bar.)
You need to charge up with sugar.
- Is it a chocolate bar? - I needed some sugar.
(A sweet first bite of the day)
(Dropping)
(His meal has disappeared in a flash.)
(Eating after blowing on it)
It's all right.
- That's fine. - You won't die.
It's all right. Boats are clean.
That's right.
- When we... - Yes?
Reach there...
Today's weather forecast has become bad.
- I heard it's not going to rain. - Right. It's not.
Everything else is fine, except for the wind.
I'll do my best.
(6:08am, arrived at the first spot)
We're here.
(Brushing his hair with determination)
(Shall I show off my skills?)
- Dowoon. - Yes?
How many webfoot octopuses do you want to catch today?
- Me? - Yes.
- A hundred? - A hundred?
At least a hundred?
Between 100 and 150.
When I go fishing,
I like sharing what I catch with people around me.
"I'll share what I catch with you guys."
This is the vibe.
- I feel really proud of it. - No way.
(He shares the raw fish he caught with his fans too.)
- You want to eat that, right? - Of course I do.
Tell me anytime.
- I'll ask you later. - I'll send it to you.
We should stay close to Dowoon.
- I know. - Exactly.
- Let's stay close. - Let's stay close.
(A flood of demands to become his friend)
- Leave the seafood to me. - My goodness!
- Gosh, we have a seafood brother. - That's right.
Seafood brother?
Na Rae, we have a new source.
- We do. All right. - We do.
(The seafood brother is getting ready to catch webfoot octopuses.)
The way I catch webfoot octopus...
is by lowering a sinker first.
What's a sinker?
It's a weight used to make the bait sink to the bottom.
There's this thing called egi attached to a sinker.
It looks like a fish,
but it has hooks attached.
I have to keep shaking it.
- I keep shaking it. - Oh, like that?
It becomes heavy when a webfoot octopus gets on it.
That's when you pull it and reel the line in.
Then you'll see a webfoot octopus on it.
It really looks like a fishing YouTube channel.
(Finally, it's his first cast.)
(Putting his leg up relaxedly)
(Dreaming of a full catch, he focuses on the tips of his fingers.)
(Grabbing)
(The fishing line begins to bounce all of a sudden.)
Is it bending?
(He reels in right away.)
- Is it here? - Is it here?
(He caught one as soon as he first cast?)
(Reeling in hard)
Oh, no.
I don't feel good about this.
(He reels in the bait awkwardly.)
The wind was strong that day,
and the current was strong too.
It was hard for me to sense the bite.
(Thinking)
I think a light sinker would be better. It's too heavy now.
(In the end, he switches the sinker.)
(Cutting it with his teeth)
(Okay, let's try it again.)
(Super focused with the readjusted fishing rod)
(Pulling lightly)
Is it a hit?
(Smiling)
(You caught one?)
Really?
Gosh, what is this?
You caught one?
(Here comes a webfoot octopus.)
- Goodness. - It's big.
- It's big. - It's big.
This one's nice.
(The new sinker)
- It's quite big. - It's big.
(Catching his first webfoot octopus in 10 minutes)
Put it in the container right away.
Go on in.
I'll try one more time.
(Throwing)
Nice.
That's quite cool.
- It must feel different. - He caught two.
Killing 2 birds with 1 stone.
(This time, he catches two at once.)
(The more confident he gets, the higher his leg goes.)
He's finally smiling.
He's having a good catch.
Gosh, this one's big.
He's gotten the hang of it.
Gosh.
(Smiling)
My shoulders are shrugging with pride.
You need to meet a good captain, indeed.
(Gosh, that punk)
(Feeling another bite)
What is this? Why is it so heavy?
(Super taut)
Gosh, what is this?
This doesn't feel like a webfoot octopus.
Gosh, this one feels good.
(Expectant)
Gosh, it's cuttlefish.
Cuttlefish!
(The radiant cuttlefish)
That's rare.
(Let me go!)
(Squirting ink)
What?
(What is this?)
Gosh, I should wash it.
(Calm)
(Keeping it in the fishing net after washing it)
This is great!
I didn't have much experience catching cuttlefish.
(The man of the sea has conquered cuttlefish as well.)
(Singing)
What is this sound?
(He keeps repeating "trot" out of the blue.)
(Here we go.)
He catches one as soon as he sinks it.
It's a field of webfoot octopuses.
(As the drummer of DAY6, he gets into the rhythm...)
(and sings, "Trot.")
(Swinging)
(He catches webfoot octopuses in a row.)
The sense of rhythm...
Gosh, this spot feels good.
- Trot - Why do you keep saying that?
When you fish, you can't help but keep casting a spell.
It's like how really thick cheese stretches.
- That's how it is. - That's a nice comparison.
I have one too, when I go carp fishing with a float.
Bite it
That's just your wish.
After that... I watched him do it.
After he goes, "Bite it,"
he says, "Darn it."
(Darn it, it didn't bite.)
"That rude carp."
(Super sulky)
(Dowoon, whose spell worked well, )
(has been fishing webfoot octopus for 3 hours.)
Three hours?
I see that it could be fun even if he does the same thing...
for three hours.
Yes, it's so much fun.
(Sea and fishing)
Gosh, this looks good.
I keep forgetting that he's a drummer.
(Laughing)
(An endless parade of webfoot octopuses)
- This one looks big. - He could catch a hundred easily.
(Happy)
Dowoon, how many have you caught so far?
I think I've caught about 50.
(He's caught 50!)
- He's caught quite a lot. - That's quite a lot.
(I'm the man of the sea.)
When I go fishing,
my mind goes blank.
I just think, "I should catch that."
"How should I manage this to catch that?"
"How high should I lift it?"
"What baits do others use?"
"It's quite windy now."
There are so many things to think about while fishing.
I think it's been really helpful for my mental health.
- It helps to clear your mind. - That's right.
How did you first get into fishing?
There was a time when I felt anxious.
I thought I should empty my mind.
The members were going through a hard time,
so we had to pause our activities for a while.
There was nothing for me to do.
I'm a drummer, right? I liked being the drummer of DAY6.
Nothing could fill the void...
- no matter what I did. - Of course."
But fishing helped me fill that void in a healthy way.
- You got through it nicely. - You did it in a healthy way.
- It's a good hobby. - Yes.
Five hours.
- Dowoon. - Yes?
- We should eat. - Shall we eat?
You should make ramyeon.
- All right. - Let's add webfoot octopuses.
You should have webfoot octopus ramyeon before you go.
All right.
- That's right! - Gosh, that sounds wonderful.
- Ramyeon. - Ramyeon!
(Choosing webfoot octopuses to put into ramyeon)
- There were a lot at the bottom. - Yes.
(I'm going to eat a lot.)
Captain. Aren't you going to eat?
Would you like to try some? Shall I share some with you?
No, we...
are going to have meat.
He's firm.
People who work at the sea have meat.
It's all set.
(It's a shame, but I'll enjoy it alone.)
Here we go.
Yes, you should only blanch it.
- Goodness. - You should have it now.
- You should have it now. - Eat it when it's slightly cooked.
- It's now. - Very slightly.
You can have a webfoot octopus like that?
Of course.
(Surprised)
(Exclaiming)
Gosh, the ink bursts out.
Right. There's ink in it.
My mouth must be all black.
(Smiling)
Oh, it's fine.
It feels like I'm watching a young man from Gyeongsang.
(The young man from Gyeongsang doesn't give in to the ink.)
(This is torturing.)
Goodness.
- The ink burst. - Gosh.
It's ink ramyeon.
(Satisfied)
- That's romantic. - It's really romantic.
(Taking a break, using the bow as his bed)
(Getting up)
(The webfoot octopus hunt hasn't ended.)
Gosh.
He looks so happy.
(A full catch of webfoot octopus)
I think I did pretty well today.
My fishing skills are still sharp.
The captain kept saying the weather forecast was bad.
But I feel like I achieved something after catching a lot.
I think I'm a true fisherman.
Is your dream to become a fisherman?
I'm thinking of keeping it as a side job.
Your final goal is becoming a captain?
Which do you like more, talking about fishing or music?
I like both.
I find both music and fishing fun.
It's 50-50. It's like how cooking is to me.
- Seriously. - It must be 50-50.
The level of his question is crazy high.
Because he loves fishing so much.
It's like asking if he likes his mom or dad more.
You wouldn't have encountered a question like this if it weren't for me.
(Honored)
- Great work. - Great job.
Yes.
(Current time: 1:49pm)
(A fishing journey that went on over 8 hours comes to an end.)
It lasts really long.
Fishing uses the whole day.
Gosh, I caught a lot.
- He caught a lot. - He did, indeed.
Why is this so big?
Fifteen.
- Gosh. - Gosh, wild cuttlefish.
I'd want that.
- Excluding the ones you ate... - I caught a lot.
Excluding them, I caught 70.
You'd eat that for three days.
(Filled)
- I want him. - Seriously.
He's such a good friend.
Count on me.
- What do you need? Count on me. - Webfoot octopus would be good.
- We need him. - Seriously.
- I'll get going now. - It was so windy.
- Great job. - Gosh.
Bye, Captain.
Great work.
(Returning after a full catch)
Captain, I'll get going!
He's cool.
He's the captain I like.
Fishing like that makes you relieve your stress, right?
It really does.
You must feel proud since you caught something.
(Getting in the car after 9 hours after relieving stress)
(He sets off without a break.)
- Hey, Dowoon. - Mom.
Yes.
It's just that I went fishing today,
and I caught a lot of webfoot octopuses,
so I want to leave them at home.
- All right. - Okay.
Bye.
Your mother rarely uses a dialect.
It's really strong sometimes,
but she didn't use much that day.
(After a call with his mom, )
(he drives on endlessly.)
What time was it?
That was around 3 to 4pm.
- Gosh. - The day is long.
It is long, indeed.
(He's been awake for 12 hours already.)
(Whistling)
- That's your parents' house. - Yes.
(He arrives at his parents' place after driving for a long time.)
Tori.
- A chicken? - They must have a dog.
That's right.
(He enters as he calls for his dog, Tori.)
(A cozy living room)
- It's a parent's home. - The vibe of a parents' home.
Gosh, the vibe of a parents' home.
(Pictures that give off the vibe of a parents' home)
"Fishing in People." Gosh.
(A kitchen that feels friendly even at a glance)
It gives off the parents' home vibe a lot.
(He arrives at his parents' place at 4:11pm.)
I love that clock.
(He quickly goes to the kitchen with the webfoot octopus.)
You have to wash off the ink?
There was a lot, so I removed it.
(This will do.)
My parents love seafood,
so when I go fishing,
I'd send what I caught to them.
I tend to give the seafood to them.
They must love it.
(He fills his parents' fridge instead of his.)
The fridge at your parents' place is always full.
That's how a fridge should look.
Tori.
- Your dog doesn't jump out? - Where is it?
(It just stays on the bed even when he calls it.)
You couldn't hear?
Oh, it must be old.
- It must be old. - Goodness.
How old is it?
It's 16 years old.
(Tori, 16 years old)
It's pretty healthy.
Live a long life.
Let's take medicine.
Gosh, there's some left.
Goodness.
Are you done?
(Filled with love)
(Grunting)
What?
They have a cat too.
- That's a cat? - Yes.
(He spends a cozy time with Hosooni as well.)
(Smiling)
(Jumping)
Look how strong it is.
(Bitter)
(Sulky)
You can't help it with cats.
Cats are rude.
I'll get going.
Seriously. They're wild.
(A man who got kicked out by Hosooni)
(Feeling lonely, he heads somewhere.)
He must be going somewhere else.
Please go home and get some rest.
He's going to Mangwon-dong.
Is he going fishing again?
- Oh, fishing by the Han River! - Fishing by the Han River!
Come on.
His day is longer than Sean's.
(He enters a basement parking lot instead of the Han River.)
(Trudging with the remaining webfoot octopus)
He must be giving it to someone.
Is he giving it to his members?
(Looking around)
(Pressing)
- Is it his member? - Maybe we'll see Young K?
- Sung Woo. - You're here.
(Sung Woo)
We haven't seen him for a long time.
(The legend of the band scene and Dowoon's respected senior)
- Yes, it's Sung Woo. - Sung Woo.
It's my respected senior, Sung Woo.
I went to the house of Nobrain's Sung Woo.
- So you're close to Sung Woo. - Yes.
He's a grateful person.
He's the senior I respect the most.
Even when we weren't that famous,
he'd call us out to eat. "Dowoon, what are you doing?"
"I'm having a meal. Do you want to join?"
It's really nice to see them together.
He always takes care of us.
He'd be like, "Dowoon, don't you need a leather jacket?"
I aspire to be like him the exact way he is.
I want to become a senior like him.
- Hey, Dowoon. - Are you busy, Sung Woo?
No, I'm not.
It's just that I caught a lot of webfoot octopuses.
Yes. You don't have to bring that for me.
Come on, Sung Woo.
Thank you.
- All right, Sung Woo. - Okay.
You must've given a lot of stuff before.
Yes, I'd give him yellowtail...
whenever I catch them.
Oh, dear. Now you have to drop by...
- Itaewon and Hannam-dong too. - I know.
- Of course. - Sure.
Why don't you just get a water tanker?
He's right. And sell them.
- That's a good idea. - Yes.
I'll buy you a water tanker.
That sounds good!
- He should, seriously. - You'd get me a water tanker?
- Can I come in? - Yes, come on in.
He hasn't changed at all.
- Let's go in. - I caught this.
- Yes. - It's a lot, though.
Goodness.
Do you run a shop or something?
Should I really?
Come on in.
Is he also from Busan?
Sung Woo is from Masan.
(The Gyeongsang men use a strong dialect...)
(as soon as they see each other.)
Is this your newlywed home?
It'll become one.
It will?
Right, that's how it was.
- Goodness. - It's so neat.
("Nobrain's Lee Sung Woo is Getting Married in October")
Is it okay for me to come in?
- How cute. - Don't bark.
- Dubu, be quiet. - How old is Dubu?
Dubu is 13.
It's the same age as Comme Des.
Can I just put it in the fridge?
I think you should...
wash the insides and remove all the ink first.
I can just put it in the fridge for now, right?
Yes, you can.
How long did you fish for that you caught this much?
You know I got skills.
This would cost a lot.
He seems really happy.
It wouldn't cost a lot.
Wild webfoot octopus must be expensive.
(He's grateful for the gift Dowoon brings every time.)
- Goodness, Sung Woo. - Have you eaten?
Eat? I think I'm going to fall asleep.
He must be tired.
You don't have anyone to eat with?
I don't really like leaving the house.
Really? But you're out already.
I don't really go out if it isn't for fishing.
I went out to fish.
Was it yellowtail?
- Oh, right. - Yellowtail and sea bream.
Once, you sent them...
and told me, "It smells like it's going to be spoiled soon,"
"so quickly grill it and eat it." So I grilled it.
(Feeling proud)
Don't you two have quite an age gap?
- How many years apart are you two? - He's 19 years older than me.
- But Sung Woo is... - He lives young.
Don't you feel uncomfortable?
- I'm not particular about it. - That's nice.
- It's not that I'm rude. - No.
I don't really mind the age.
Older guys like that better.
- Yes, thank you so much. - That's right.
If you get along well, age doesn't matter.
It really doesn't matter.
You'll come to my wedding, right?
Oh, right. Of course, I will.
If you don't come after saying that you will...
I emptied my schedule. These days...
I'll give you my wedding invitation.
- Really? - My wedding invitation.
A wedding invitation.
I'll treasure it like a family treasure.
(Solemn)
(A man who gives up his knees upon receiving the invitation)
Who takes a wedding invitation on his knees?
- My wife-to-be... - Yes?
Designed everything and put the sticker... Oh, she didn't.
Here.
(Readily taking it)
- The man I admire the most. - Don't do that.
(Embarrassed)
Try not showing up and see what happens.
I'll write your name down on my death note right away.
You should open it, though.
- Gosh, it's... - Open it! Your senior...
- I wanted to save it for later. - You're not even opening it?
I wanted to save it for later.
(Impressed)
I knew it.
(How is it?)
- "After a long wait..." - Stop it.
"After a long wait..."
(Stop!)
- "The two of us..." - No.
(The man from Gyeongsang can't tolerate awkwardness.)
Don't use it as a ramyeon coaster.
- It does like people. - It's really funny.
It likes you.
It likes when its butt is patted.
It once caused a sensation...
- It was popular? - as a singing dog.
It can sing?
(Dubu was once the talk of the town as a singing dog.)
- That's right. - You're so good.
(The father is proud.)
There are a few songs that Dubu likes.
One of them is...
(Playing Dubu's favorite song)
- Look at its face. - It's getting ready.
Stand by.
(Could it actually sing?)
Does it still sing?
(The dog singer listens to the song first.)
(Howling)
(I can't believe this is possible!)
(Singing its heart out alongside the song)
(Clapping)
(Everyone, watch our Dubu!)
He keeps a good rhythm.
- How is that possible? - Tell me about it.
- It's so fascinating. - How is that possible?
(Eyes of respect)
It has a favorite part.
(Will it sing this part too?)
Dubu.
(Turning away)
It lost its focus.
After it got older,
- it started to lose focus. - But it's old.
It sang the first part well.
Its focus... Anyway, that's how it is.
Dubu likes this song.
It suddenly changed its expression.
Its expression was like... It suddenly lit up.
It's Dubu's special talent.
(It lit up as soon as its favorite song played.)
- It suddenly lit up like this. - It has a few songs it likes.
- It becomes happy when it's played. - Goodness.
It really is a dog singer.
It's a musician.
It carries my genes.
No, not my genes exactly.
It takes after my soul with my money.
- That's right, Sung Woo. - Right.
It's so cute.
I'll get going now. Thank you so much. My goodness.
- I'll see you on the tenth. - All right.
Drive safe.
All right. Don't forget that.
Forget what?
- Freeze the webfoot octopus. - All right.
- I'll get going. - Okay.
Dowoon.
(Giving a heart all of a sudden)
During our concert, I cried really hard and...
- I saw that. - While crying...
Because I love my fans so much,
I wanted to express my love.
- I did this. - Oh, Sung Woo imitated that?
He imitated me and teased me.
I almost imitated it without knowing.
I thought it was a way Gen MZ says goodbye.
(Laughing)
(Exchanging goodbyes of love with Sung Woo)
- See you. - I'll get going.
- Goodbye. - I'll get going.
- He's polite to older guys. - Bye.
(After sharing a deep friendship,)
(Dowoon returns home.)
He must be tired.
He should get some sleep now.
What time is it?
- How long has he been awake for? - I know.
(The day of the man of the sea, Wake up and leave house)
(He got up at 2:40am.)
(Fisherman Do left his house at 3:30am.)
(Webfoot octopus fishing went on for eight hours.)
(Fishing)
(He drove by himself and shared webfoot octopus...)
(for five hours.)
(Delivering webfoot octopus)
(He returned home after 17 hours.)
Seventeen hours?
- He must be sleepy. - I was sleepy, indeed.
(I'm sleepy, but I should get the job done.)
(He takes the fishing gear...)
(and goes to the bathroom.)
Oh, you need to wash those.
I just need to rinse it with water.
It's easier than you think.
(Washing off the salt by rubbing it with hands)
(With utmost sincerity)
You can't overlook the saltiness.
Yes, if you don't wash it, it becomes really icky.
(He doesn't forget to remove water.)
(Spacing out)
(Cleaning it like crazy while fighting off exhaustion)
You can't do that if you don't like it.
Of course not.
You wouldn't clean those when you're exhausted.
(Carrying the fishing gear he cherishes)
(Heave-ho)
He sorts them out too.
I think you're amazing.
- Really? - It's not easy to do that.
Yes.
(It took him an hour to clean up his gear.)
- He needs to wash now. - It's his first time washing today.
It's almost 10pm.
(Splash)
(Tapping)
He's so manly.
(The spicy tapping of the man of the sea)
(After a short yet impactful skincare)
(Tired)
(Struggling)
(He relaxes his body after 19 hours.)
(Silent)
Today?
It was meaningful and pleasant.
It was fun, and I was happy.
I did fishing really comfortably.
I did fishing well pleasantly next to the reliable captain.
- Dowoon. - I shared it well with my friend.
I think mental health is the most important.
I think fishing helps the most.
It gives me strength...
to go on.
What?
He'd just sleep like that?
(A Breather for the Mind, Take a Beat, then Ba-dum)
That was great.
(That was great.)
Goodness. Thank you.
I should do something on my day off like him.
I was envious of that too.
Falling that deeply into a hobby...
- Of course. - That's right.
Could make you happy.
- Also, his eyes were glistening. - That's right.
He was immersed in his clip too.
- That's right. - When he was fishing?
I have huge respect.
Actually, having a healthy hobby...
- helps with your music career. - That's right.
- That's right. - It really does.
It took me really long to figure that out.
I feel like he knows that well,
so I found him cool,
- and I was envious. - Thank you.
I want to try fishing, though.
Tell me anytime if you need seafood.
- I'll give it to you. - I'll look forward to getting it.
All right. Tell me anytime.
(Next story)
I was so scared.
(Sung Hwan is in a mysterious machine.)
(Gosh, it's nerve-racking.)
(I should've come earlier.)
(I came to the clinic because of leukoplakia.)
It affects my eyebrows.
(His eyes, nose, and mouth)
(White spots spread across the face)
(It's serious.)
(It's gotten worse.)
(It's incurable, )
(so there's no guarantee that you'll get better.)
(I'll get rid of it while I'm at the clinic.)
Goodness!
(I need to overcome this!)
Gosh, it hurts.
(I feel like I'm going to die.)
(That was tough.)
(Opening)
(Shall I refresh my mood?)
I think it's been over ten years.
(Goodbye to the days of wearing the same outfit.)
(Putting it on)
(Transforming into the Beverly Hills style)
(Gosh, this can't fit.)
(This is bad.)
(There aren't any clothes that fit me.)
(Even the staff is flustered.)
(The store has become busy finding the clothes that fit him.)
The size would've been perfect if I'd lost 15kg.
(Finding Mister Ku's Lost Size)
(MINHO is heading somewhere excitedly?)
(Hello)
(Uncle MINHO is here.)
(MINHO's favorite restaurant...)
(with a warm and friendly atmosphere)
(He's used to it.)
(Homemade-style side dishes)
(I'm a lucky guy.)
(Ecstatic)
(In a trance)
(Is he finally done with his meal?)
(I'll refill one more bowl.)
(Let's eat as though this was my first bowl.)
(It's perfect.)
(Beeping)
(While looking at the scenery outside, )
(he enjoys his free time to the fullest.)
(He arrived at his favorite cafe.)
(And his favorite, ssanghwatang)
(Sipping up the energy)
(Impressed)
(Scraping the remaining)
(Energy fully charged)
(Gosh, the weather is great.)
(Shall I go for a light walk?)
(Light)
(MINHO's Favorite Day)